You and I should stop meeting each other.
I set the fire.
…and was arrested at the scene.
Arson? What's happening?
Right now, your father
is on the edge between life and death
in the hospital where he was taken.
Then does it mean you didn't visit
the house with the intent of arson?
I didn't.
Masaki Nogi is hiding something?
-We also detected gasoline on it.
-Gasoline…
A new report from a witness
in the neighborhood.
Ms. Nishimura!
Masaki Nogi lost consciousness
in his cell, vomiting blood!
He may not last long.
I came back to see you.
Want to run away?
Let's run away.
Just the two of us.
I want to be with you.
I want to see that starry sky…
with you alone.
Sorry.
I was just kidding.
Of course, you're kidding.
I'd be arrested if I did
something like that.
The interrogation is canceled for now
so you have plenty of time to rest.
When I get better…
the questioning will start again, huh?
I understand.
I'll go to sleep.
That was the second crime…
Here's your ticket.
PAY FARE IN ADVANCE
Go ahead.
Please fasten your seatbelts.
The bus will depart in five minutes.
…I ever committed.
We will depart shortly.
For your safety,
please keep your seatbelt fastened
while the vehicle is moving.
That was my second…
crime.
NAGANO
-Hello.
-I'm sorry to bother you so early.
We can't locate Mr. Nogi in Room 502.
He was there
when we checked the rooms last night,
but was gone when I came to take
his temperature this morning.
We're now looking for him.
I see.
I'll be there immediately.
Thank you.
I heard Masaki Nogi disappeared.
Yes. I've got the report.
Why? Where's Ms. Nishimura?
She sent me an e-mail to say
she can't work today due to a fever.
Tell her we need to keep in touch
in an emergency like this.
Yes.
Uh, branch chief?
What?
Were you aware of their relationship?
What relationship?
Between Ms. Nishimura and Masaki Nogi.
What do you mean?
They knew each other
when they were college students.
And they were probably
romantically involved.
Call her now.
Yes.
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this time.…
Her cell phone is switched off.
Hello.
Is this the residence
of Ms. Nishimura, the prosecutor?
Yes, it is.
I'm Ohata, from the Chuo Branch
of Yokohama District
Public Prosecutors Office.
Kanade speaks well of you.
I'm Okuda,
Kanade's fiancé.
It's nice to talk to you.
Is Ms. Nishimura home?
Uh, yes.
The assistant officer says
he received a message from her
saying she has a fever
and can't come to work today.
But we have an urgent matter
so I called this number.
I see.
She seems to have turned off her phone,
and we can't get a hold of her.
I'm really sorry,
but she just fell asleep.
I think she needs to rest.
Oh, I see.
Should I wake her?
No, that's not necessary.
Then when she gets up,
would you please tell her
to contact me as soon as possible?
I certainly will.
Goodbye.
She's sleeping at home.
You're okay with that?
Our top priority now is to find Nogi.
Apply for the cancellation
of detainment suspension.
Yes.
Thank you for riding with us.
We've arrived at Kofu.
Remember to take all your belongings
when you leave the bus.
The next stop is our final stop,
Matsumoto.
Are you okay? Are you in any pain?
I'm so happy, I want to get up and dance.
Hey.
Let me have your shoulder.
Does anybody know…
that you're here?
Who's the one who said we should run away?
Me.
That's the end of the interview.
We'll contact you later with the result.
Thank you very much.
I hope I did well.
Don't worry.
You got a recommendation from Mr. Nogi.
Um…
Do you know how he is doing now?
I've heard he hasn't
regained consciousness yet.
That was a very shocking incident.
Yes.
Mr. Umeda, have you heard?
A-About what?
About his son who was arrested.
His detainment had been suspended
because his health deteriorated,
but apparently,
he has escaped from the hospital.
Huh?
The Kanagawa Prefectural Police
have an emergency deployment to find him.
Doctor, thank you for waiting.
I know you're busy.
It's fine.
So you're saying
you still don't know where Masaki is?
We checked the security cameras
in the hospital.
We saw him leave from the side entrance
early in the morning.
But we don't know where he went.
Nogi has gallbladder cancer, right?
Yes.
I want your opinion
as his attending physician.
Do you think he could run away
in his physical condition?
He was just admitted as an emergency
due to vomiting blood.
Wouldn't he have trouble
even trying to walk?
It is true
that he underwent endoscopic treatment.
He might be developing anemia.
I don't think it's likely he can get far.
What if somebody is with him?
I guess it would be easier with assistance
as opposed to being on his own.
I see.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
If you'd excuse me.
Doctor.
Excuse me for intruding on your privacy,
but I believe you are engaged
to Prosecutor Nishimura.
Yes.
I heard she is staying home sick today.
Please give my regards to her.
We're working together on this case.
I'll do that.
Goodbye.
Kanade is with Masaki now?
-Why?
-Listen.
I heard about Masaki
at the interview today.
So I rushed to call Kanade,
but her phone was turned off.
Her office told me she's off today.
Are you serious?
Hey, Mom!
We're out of soap!
You can use my body soap!
-Is it all right?
-Yes. It's okay.
If they had to suspend his detention…
it must mean it's pretty serious.
I'm sure his condition is really bad.
What in the world…
Huh?
I can't believe it.
What in the world are they doing?
I hope nobody dies.
-Why would you say that?
-Sorry.
I don't want to lose anybody else.
I couldn't bear it.
Tomo. It's ringing.
Hey.
Huh?
Hello.
Here you are.
Pardon me for visiting so late at night.
No worries.
Actually, I have something
I want to ask you about Kanade.
It's the opposite, isn't it?
Hmm?
You know.
From back then.
Yeah, it is.
The Shinshu fireworks are canceled,
as we thought.
Kaori and Yuki said they couldn't make it.
Oh yeah?
What are we going to do?
Want to stay here for a while?
Huh? Why?
Instead of fireworks…
I'm turning them off.
Yeah.
The sky, the stars,
and the darkness were the same.
I've never seen…
such a beautiful starry sky.
First time for me too.
Kanade.
I love you.
What was different from before
was not only that I was sitting
in the driver's seat.
We were both 35 years old already,
and he was a suspect on the run.
And I was the prosecutor in charge.
I'm relieved.
Hmm?
I was worried the stars
wouldn't be out tonight.
That's what you were worried about?
Although we're fugitives?
Not about getting caught?
Were you worried?
No, I wasn't.
You know I never worry about things.
When I'm with you,
your idiocy rubs off on me.
That's harsh.
My dream came true.
Do you remember telling me
those days were the happiest times
in your life?
Mm-hmm.
I feel the same way.
That period was
the happiest time of my life.
Though it was so short.
It went by
in the blink of an eye.
But…
I treasure it.
So just for now…
can you stay like this?
I don't mind dying
if I'm with you, Kanade.
I wish I could die right now.
Don't be silly.
Is it silly?
Everybody dies someday.
When you die…
you turn into a star.
Didn't anyone…
tell you that
when you were a kid?
No.
I was told that.
By whom?
Who told you? Masaki?
I'm still alive.
Good.
I haven't slept so well in a long time.
Really?
It's probably because you were with me.
Masaki.
The truth is you haven't had one day
that you could just relax
since Kaori passed away, right?
How come?
Because that's who you are.
While others might seal off their memories
and pretend to forget,
you could never forget.
That's not true.
You're not shrewd enough
to act like nothing happened.
I think you're wrong.
-I'm--
-That's why you went overseas
and did volunteer work,
resulting in damage to your health.
Masaki.
I want to ask you something.
I was determined to do one thing.
Even if I was forced out
of the prosecutor's office,
I had to save Masaki.
I had to seek out the truth.
Masaki.
You're hiding something, right?
Her cell phone is still turned off.
Branch chief, is this really okay?
If she's with him now,
wouldn't it be a major problem?
But her fiancé clearly said
that she's resting at home.
We can't just barge into the home
of a prosecutor absent due to illness.
But what if the police decide to go in?
The only thing that would happen
is I'd get fired.
Branch chief.
Don't worry.
As an assistant officer,
you wouldn't experience any issues.
That's not what I meant, though…
KANADE NISHIMURA
Yes.
I see.
So where are you now?
Understood.
I'll inform the Yokohama Minami Police.
Ms. Nishimura is in Nagano Prefecture.
She said she has taken
Masaki Nogi into custody.
What?
Looks like her fever has subsided.
I'll arrange for detention right away.
INBOX
KANADE NISHIMURA
Please allow me just one day.
I'm going to find out the truth.
What a gutsy one
this daughter of Eisuke Tsuji is.
MAIL DELETED
Kanade.
Hmm?
Were you going to take me back all along?
Well,
I still haven't heard the truth from you.
Masaki,
you didn't really set the fire.
Isn't that right?
Why are you so obsessed?
It's my job to seek the truth.
Even if…
I said I did it?
Yes.
If it's not the truth.
The truth… huh?
Hmm?
Hey, Kanade.
What is "truth"?
Will I be getting handcuffed again?
Then I prefer
to be handcuffed by you, Kanade.
Stop it.
"Stop it."
"Don't be silly."
I'm always getting scolded by you,
aren't I?
Masaki.
Don't die.
Please.
Promise me.
Don't go away again.
That promise…
might be…
difficult to make.
No, you have to.
Promise me.
The way to hold hands
that can never be separated.
Handcuffs.
Do you know there's a way to hold hands
that can never be separated?
Use handcuffs?
That was quite an accomplishment,
Ms. Nishimura.
I apologize.
Oh, that was a genuine praise.
After all, you apprehended
a fleeing suspect all on your own.
Is it true that Masaki Nogi
is refusing treatment?
Yes.
After his health is checked
at the hospital,
we will take him to detention.
Are you feeling any discomfort?
No.
I'm feeling fine.
Come on in.
Won't surgery be necessary?
Yes, his doctor says as soon as possible.
I see.
Branch chief.
I still don't think
Masaki Nogi is the arsonist.
On what basis?
Did you get a confession?
No.
Then gather the evidence to prove it.
Reconfirm the origin of the fire.
Follow up with the witnesses.
Keep investigating.
Yes.
Goodbye.
INVESTIGATION WILL CONTINUE
NM WILL BE DETAINED
MESSAGE
SENDING…
DELETE 1 MESSAGE?
YES/NO
DELETED
Have a good evening, ma'am.
Still using a flip phone? How rare.
-Doctor.
-Thank you.
KAJI
MESSAGE RECEIVED
INVESTIGATION WILL CONTINUE
NM WILL BE DETAINED
DELETE MESSAGE
CALL HISTORY
TOMO, YUKI, TAKASHI, KAJI
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M WORRIED. CALL ME.
What are you doing? Where are you?
Masaki's with you, isn't he?
Huh?
Who told you? Why?
He didn't just tell me.
Takashi…
came over here.
What?
He was worried about you,
and came to ask if we knew anything.
He was pretty sure
you were with Masaki.
So that's why.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
But I brought back Masaki.
I'm home now and…
Kanade?
Hello? Kanade? Can you hear me?
Hello?
Kanade?
I WON'T BE HOME FOR A WHILE.
WE SHOULD BREAK UP.
I knew this would happen from the start.
I was prepared
for this to happen when I left. But…
Good morning.
Thank you for bringing Nogi into custody.
Not at all.
How is Masaki Nogi doing?
No big changes so far, I heard.
If he suddenly deteriorates,
take him to the hospital.
Understood.
Then let's start.
Yes.
FORENSIC REPORT
We checked with the forensic team again.
As we thought in this case,
the fire originated
from the side of the garage
of Nogi's residence.
This part.
It's where the burned piece
of a plastic fuel can was found.
We detected gasoline around the area.
It doesn't match Masaki Nogi's statement,
which was that the curtains
in the living room caught fire.
Any new witnesses
for the suspicious person?
The security cameras at the house
were burned up in the fire
and no data remained.
We are now checking
security cameras in the neighborhood.
I was already asked by the detective too,
but someone yelled, "What are you doing?"
That made the person run away, it seemed.
In which direction?
From Mr. Nogi's house,
that way.
Which way from here?
-Here… we turn left.
-Left.
I heard a voice calling, "There's a fire,"
so I hurried outside.
I saw a man run away.
Did the man look like this?
I don't know.
I think he was wearing a suit.
-He was wearing a suit?
-Yes.
That's D50, the Kano residence.
The Kano residence is…
-Right there.
-Yes.
Alright.
Here.
How is it going?
As you've said,
I haven't been able to find anyone either.
The garage of the house is in a blind spot
from all the security cameras in the area.
That's the problem.
Oh, this is for you.
Thank you very much.
Here.
-Thank you.
-No matter how many times
I review the footage,
all I see is the dry cleaner's car.
Oh, it must be
their delivery car for this area.
-What?
-Huh?
Detective Watanabe,
wouldn't this car have a dashcam?
Yes, they usually have one on board.
We need to know the registration number,
the company, and to identify the driver!
These came for you.
They're from a lawyer named Yuki Umeda.
Thank you.
Do you really want to refuse visitations?
Yes.
YOKOHAMA MINAMI POLICE STATION
YOKOHAMA DISTRICT
PUBLIC PROSECUTORS OFFICE
-Ms. Nishimura.
-Yes.
The dashcam turned up something.
It might be this man.
September 1st.
At 10:06 p.m.
Right after the fire broke out.
This matches the eyewitness accounts
regarding clothing and appearance.
But it's hard to make out the face
based on this image.
-Can we see a close-up?
-Yes.
Hey, Kanade.
What is "truth"?
What brings you here so suddenly?
Well…
Yuki.
I'm sorry, Tomo.
But there is
something I have to ask, so I will.
Yuki.
That night…
when there was a fire at Mr. Nogi's house,
what were you doing in front of the house?
You were recorded on a dashcam.
This is you, right?
Yuki?
What is this?
Masaki…
tried to cover it up…
for me.
Masaki.
Yuki, did you…
No, Masaki.
-I…
-Just go.
-But…
-Hurry!
He covered for me, and…
Hey, what's going on?
You have a guest over?
Uhh… Umm…
Subtitle translation by: Ikuko Sachs
That case and the arson…
Aren't they all connected in some way?
Don't stick your nose into this matter.
I can let you live or die.
Shut up!
I don't have any time left.
Doesn't it look like a human face?
It was a fuel can.
Please tell me the truth.